Okay, help me out here.
How does an archeology professor get that good with a whip?
Maybe he took a class at the adult bookstore.
That's how I learned.
I can't believe you've never seen  Raiders of the Lost Ark.
And I can't believe you've never read  Eat, Pray, Love.
When she comes out with
Eat, Pray, Run Away From A   Giant Boulder, I'll read it.
I don't care if Eat, Pray, Love changed your life,
I'm not reading it.
You know, I could totally rock a hat like that.
That's the work of noted Hollywood costume designer
Deborah Nadoolman.
She also designed
the iconic red and black jacket
in Michael Jackson's Thriller video,
which I've never viewed in its entirety,
as I find zombies dancing
in choreographed synchronicity implausible.
And also, it's really scary.
Would someone please turn off the Sheldon commentary track?
There's no switch. Just listen and learn.
Penny, if you think this is good,
you should come with us Friday
to see it on the big screen at the Colonial.
Well, I'm watching it now.
Why would I want to see it again on Friday?
Because the print they're showing on Friday
has an additional 21 seconds of previously unseen footage.
What? 21 seconds? That'll be like seeing a whole new movie!
Exactly.
They say it finally solves the submarine controversy.
Did-- Leonard?
I'm no expert, but I believe
what we just heard from Penny was sarcasm.
Oh! Good.
I'm 8 for 26 this month.
Yeah, I think I'll pass.
But you guys enjoy your extra 21 seconds.
Bet if I could make you understand
why this is such a cool thing, we'd still be together.
Mm, yeah, no, we wouldn't.
Uh-huh.
I'm guessing 21 seconds had something to do with that, too.
May I point out to you all
that the screening is "first come, first served"?
Relax, it's 5:00. The movie doesn't start till midnight.
Another way of saying that is
"the movie starts at midnight, and it's already 5:00."
Let's go.
You know, if we miss it, we'll have the fun of
listening to Sheldon whine about it for the rest of our lives.
See? Howard's on my side.
Actually, I'm not.
I'm using sarcasm to mock you.
Drat. Now I'm 8 for 27.
Don't worry, Sheldon.We'll be fine.
What happened to the Leonard Hofstadter
who waited in line with me for 14 hours
to see the midnight premiere of Star Trek: Nemesis?
Oh. Well, he waited in line for 14 hours,
while you napped in a lawn chair,
he got in a fight with a Klingon
when he stepped out of line to pee
and you wouldn't wake up to vouch for him,
and worst of all, he saw Star Trek: Nemesis.
But how were our seats?
Excellent.
I rest my case.
Amy, don't you agree we should leave now and get in line?
Actually, as the newest member of your social group,
I believe I'll gain more acceptance by arbitrarily
siding with your friends from time to time.
Shrewd.
Leonard, you're right.
We should enjoy our meal, arrive late,
and risk winding up with terrible seats,
assuming we get in at all.
Thank you, Amy.
See? It's working.
Knock-knock.
Who's there?
Olive.[I love u]
Olive you, too.
Guys, that's really starting to get old.
Knock-knock.
Who's there?
I have a girlfriend and you don't.
Hysterical!
Wait, now, we don't know that yet. He isn't finished.
I have a girlfriend and you don't who?
So. Are you sure you don't want to come with us to Raiders?
Oh, no. That movie has melting faces.
It reminds me too much of the time
I dropped that vial of flesh-eating bacteria
into the Rhesus monkey lab.
Besides, Penny and I are having a girls' night tonight.
Girls' night?  What does that entail?
Oh, you know, girls get together,
hang out, share girl talk.
I'm a girl.
Oh. Well, maybe you can join us. I'll ask Penny.
No need. Penny and I are very close.
You are?
Yes. In fact, our menses are synchronized.
Penny.
Bernadette tells me you're planning a girls' night.
I'm a girl.
Oh. Um, it was -- it was just going to be me and Bernadette.
Besides, I thought you were going to the movies
with Sheldon and the guys.
Yes, but they're not girls.
I'm a girl.
Yeah, no, no, I-I-I got that.
What's the dress code?
Uh, just wear something comfortable.
All right. I'll have to go shopping.
Knock-knock.
Who is there?
- Hugh.  - Hugh who?
Hugh people need to listen to me.
It's time to get in line for the movie.
And that's how you tell a knock-knock joke.
Under normal circumstances I'd say, "I told you so".
But as I have told you so
with such vehemence and frequency already,
the phrase has lost all meaning.
Therefore, I will be replacing it with the phrase:
"I informed you thusly".
Ooh. Can't wait for that to start.
I informed you thusly.
8 for 28.
This is where we could have been
if we hadn't stopped for dinner.
if Koothrappali hadn't ordered dessert.
Well I earned it, dude, I ate all my broccoli.
And here's where we are. The runts in a large litter.
Unlikely to ever reach
the nourishing teats of Indiana Jones.
So I guess it's a good thing we stopped for dinner.
You know, guys, when facing disappointment,
Eat, Pray, Loveteaches us --
Oh, shut up.
...So anyway, to make a long story short,
turns out I have an unusually firm cervix.
You know -- Amy, when we say "girl talk",
it doesn't just have to be about our lady parts.
Shame. 'Cause I have a real zinger
about my tilted uterus.
Penny, your nails look great.
Oh, thanks. I found this place in Alhambra.
It's in a woman's basement.
I think it's a front for human trafficking,
but they do a really good job.
A colleague of mine did her graduate thesis on the fungus
that grows on improperly sterilized manicure implements.
Well don't tell me that's not "girl talk".
So where should we go tonight?
A bar? A club? A movie?
Or we could just stay here.
Yes, a continue to bond.
I have a feeling that after tonight,
one of you will become my best friend forever.
Or "BFF," if you prefer.
Which I don't.
All right, time to open Bachelor Number Two.
Gee, I don't know if I should drink more.
I have to drive home, and I've got enough trouble
seeing over the dashboard as it is.
That's okay. You can just sleep here.
Oh, good, a slumber party!
We'll do makeovers, initiate phony phone calls,
and have spirited pillow fights in our frilly nighties!
Oh, gosh, Amy.
I don't know if I would call this an actual slumber party.
Well, that's disappointing.
I've always wanted to be invited to a slumber party.
Oh, you never were?
Not even when you were a kid?
Well, there was the time I had my tonsils out,
and I shared a room with a little Vietnamese girl.
She didn't make it through the night,
but up till then, it was kind of fun.
Okay. Well, I guess we're having a slumber party.
Pillow fight!
Oh, I hope they let us in soon.
I'm tired of running to the gas station to use the bathroom.
The guy makes me buy a Gatorade every time.
It's a vicious circle.
Too bad you don't have a stadium pal like me.
What's a stadium pal?
Let me put it this way:
takes care of the bathroom problem,
and it keeps your calf warm.
Hey, guys, bad news. I just did a quick calculation.
Given the size of the theater and the length of this line,
we might not get seats.
What did he say?
Nice going, Raj.
Just got him down for his nap.
We might not get seats?!
It's fine, it's fine.Go back to sleep.
Oh, I informed you thusly! I so informed you thusly.
Howard, you talk to him.
Howard?
You're peeing, aren't you?
Hey, look who's here!
Hey, buddies!
Well, if it isn't Wil Wheaton,
the Jar Jar Binks of the Star Trek universe.
(la Ja Ja Binks)Mee-sa think that very funny!
Well, you-sa can go think that at the back of the line.
No cuts, no buts, no coconuts.
Wil Wheaton.
Yeah.
I'm a big fan.
Of what? Poorly executed beards?
Do you think you could get me and my friends into the movie?
We got here a little late.
No problem. Come on, I'll hook you up.
Awesome.
We-sa gonna go into the movie now! Bye-bye!
This is Indiana Jones,
not Star Trek.
There should be no value to his pseudo-celebrity here!
And even at Star Trek conventions,
they only let him in if he helps set up!
Calm down, Sheldon.
I will not calm down.
This affront to justice and decency cannot go unanswered.
As Captain Jean-Luc Picard once said,
"The line must be drawn here!
"This far, no farther!"
Had to wake him up from his nap, didn't you?
You know what I really love about Howard?
His chest hair.
Howard has a hairy chest?
No, just the one.
But it's really long.
Okay, there you go-- Sultry Sunrise Red.
What do you think?
My nails have never looked so pretty before.
Get it off.
Oh, oh, uh, looks like they're getting ready
to let people in.
Listen to what Mr. Wil Wheaton is tweeting.
"Best seats in house for Raiders screening.
Suck on that, Sheldon Cooper."
Why do you read his Twitter feed?
You know it's only going to upset you.
I believe in knowing my enemy, Leonard.
Had Twitter existed at the time, would not General Custer
have followed the tweets of Sitting Bull?
Would not Lee have followed Grant?
Would not Spy have followed Spy?
I have more examples, but excuse me.
Hello.
Well, this seems like an odd time
to test my cell phone quality, but go on.
Test phrases? All right.
Im a tote.
Ulba.
Twad.
All together?
I'm a total buttwad.
Why are you laughing?
Hello?
And that, girls, is how you make a phony phone call.
I'm not sure I grasp
the full entertainment value, but all right.
Next on Wikipedia's list of slumber party activities:
"Truth or Dare."
Okay, it's your game. You go first.
Hang on. I'm familiarizing myself with the rules.
Seems fairly straightforward.
Bernadette, truth or dare?
- Truth. - All right.
To what temperature must you heat beef
in order to kill the prion
that cses bovinespongiform encephalopathy?
Um...
Remember, you have to answer honestly.
Wait. No, Amy, you're supposed to ask her
something personal or embarrassing.
Oh. All right.
What is the circumference of your areolas?
"Munching on complimentary popcorn.
Woot, woot."
Oh, the gall.
I hope his next tweet is  "Popcorn lodged in trachea.
Choking to death.
Woot, woot."
Guys, I am sorry.We are full up.
No!
We're full up.
We really want to see this.
Isn't there anything you can do?
Sorry. Fire regulations.
Should've gotten here earlier.
This is nothing but ablatant abuse of power
by a petty functionary.
Explain to me why Wil Wheaton and his lackeys
get in and we don't.
'Cause I'm the petty functionary with a clipboard, bitch.
I guess that's that.
Let's go home.
You know what? I'm going back to "I told you so."
I told you so.
We can still see something.
Oh, the new Sandra Bullock movie is playing two blocks away.
You know Sandy B. always brings it.
Look-- a side door.
Come on, Short Round.
I guess we'd bettergo after him.
Short Round?
Indy's young sidekick from Temple of Doom.
Yeah, I know who itis, but why is it me?
You're right. It shouldbe a cuddly Asian boy.
Like me.
"And Absalom has kissed her nether eye,
"And Nicholas is branded on the butt.
This tale is done, and God save all the rout."
What the hell was that?
Bernadette dared me to tell a dirty story.
"The Miller's Tale" by Chaucer is the dirtiest story I know.
It would have been hidden in sock drawers
if people in the 14th century had worn socks.
I thought it was pretty spicy.
Especially the part where he kisses her nether eye.
You might not like it as much
if you knew what "nether eye" meant.
Hint: if one cares about hygiene,
one ought not be kissing it.
Okay, my turn.
Penny, truth or dare?
Truth.
Why are you still hanging out with Leonard so much
even though you broke up with him?
Oh, that's an excellent question.
For two people who claim to be no longer pair-bonded,
you spend an inordinate amount of time in each other's company.
Yeah.
Dare.
I don't believe the rules allow
for an ex post facto option change.
Yeah.
Okay, look, just because we're not seeing each other anymore
doesn't meanwe can't be friends.
I mean, Leonard's a great guy.
Then, why did you terminate your relationship with him?
I don't know.
He got really serious, and I wasn't ready for it.
Interesting.
How will you react if, in the future,
you become ready for it, and Leonard is unavailable,
because another woman has realized that he is--
to use your words--"a great guy"?
You can only ask one question.
That one.
You know what,  I don't want to play anymore.
Well, I'm not sure how this is scored,
but I believe we may have won.
Sheldon?
Where did he go?
We're looking for Sheldon,not Marmaduke.
You whistled?
What is that?
Raiders of the Lost Ark
with 21 additional seconds.
If I can't see it, no one else can see it.
Sheldon, this is crazy.
No. Crazy was leaving the projection booth unattended.
Listen to me.
You are over-tired. You're not thinking right.
Put the movie back before we get into trouble.
Trouble is my middle name,Leonard.
Actually, it's Lee,but I prefer Trouble.
Oh, look who they let in.
Don't worry, Wil Wheaton. I was just leaving.
Come on, Short Round.
Yeah.
Come on, guys! Hurry up! Hurry up!
Let's see you run with a bag of urines trapped to your leg.
He's got the movie! Get him!
Why is there never a pontoon plane when you need one?
She's been in there a long time.
Clearly, losing Truth or Dare upset her.
Perhaps we should try to take her mind off it
with anothor popular slumber party activity.
- Ooh, like what? - Well, the Internet suggests
that slumber party guests often engage
in harmless experimentation with lesbianism.
Where exactly on the Internet have you been looking?
- Penny?  - Oh, hey, Amy.
Look, I'm sorry I got so upset. I just...
What are you doing?
Don't worry. I'll avoid the nether eye.
I might have gone with eating raw cookie dough.